Guide to Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art special events records, 1891-2010 COR0003.4.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Dailies, Circa 1985 - 2010; Series 13
  - 1869 Society/Fonseca Preview Reception, 2004 October 7; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 36)
  - Fellows Fonseca Reception, 2004 October 8; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 37)
  - Mariam Wedding Reception, 2004 October 9; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 38)
  - Lufthansa German Airlines, 2004 October 13; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 39)
  - Georgetown University Law Center, 2004 October 16; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 40)
  - Luse, Gorman, Pomerenk and Schick, 2004 October 18; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 41)
  - Julia J. Norrell Director's Circle Reception, 2004 October 19; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 42)
  - Julia Norrell New/Upper Level Opening, 2004 October 20; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 43)
  - Aon Re Worldwide, 2004 October 24; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 44)
  - BPW Luncheon, 2004 October 26; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 45)
  - Special Events Fall Preview, 2004 October 28; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 46)
  - Curator's Journal Project Reception, 2004 November 4; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 47)
  - American Public Health Association, 2004 November 9; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 48)
  - Smithsonian Associates Reception, 2004 November 11; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 49)
  - Friends Benefit "ArtCentric 04", 2004 November 12; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 50)
  - Parent's Weekend Lunch Breakfast, 2004 November 13; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 51)
  - 1869 Fall Party, 2004 November 20; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 52)
  - Duane Morris LLP, 2004 November 30; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 53)
  - Dewey Ballantine, 2004 December 7; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 54)
  - Campaign Prospect Dinner, 2004 December 6; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 55)
  - The Scientist Cancelled, 2004 December 6; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 56)
  - The Wallace Foundation, 2004 December 1; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 57)
  - AFCEA - Washington Chapter, 2004 December 8; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 58)
  - Chairman's Guild Holiday Party, 2004 December 9; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 59)
  - Chermayeff Reception, 2004 December 9; Series 13 (Box 88, Folder 60)
  - General Electirc, 2004 December 10; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Welch/Salemme Wedding Ceremony and Reception, 2004 December 11; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - General Dynamics, 2004 December 12; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - Office of Personnel Managemnet, 2004 December 14; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - Corcoran Staff Party, 2004 December 16; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Docent Holiday Party, 2004 December 16; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - Capital One Financial Corporation, 2004 December 17; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - Hunton Williams, 2004 December 18; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - BPW Luncheon, 2005 January 11; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - The Advisory Board Company, 2005 January 14; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - SAIC, 2005 January 22; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - Chermayeff Reception, 2005 January 25; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Mary Lyn Kotz Reception, 2005 January 26; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - NFAA Fundraiser, 2005 January 31; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - WHNPA, 2005 February 4-6; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - American Trucking Association, Inc., 2005 Febrruary 7; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - Fonseca Art Forum Luncheon, 2005 February 8; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - Horace Mann Elementary School, 2005 February 25; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - 1869 Spring Balck Tie, 2005 February 26; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - WPA\C Auction Opening, 2005 February 24; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - WPA\C Gala, 2005 March 5; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - Scholarship Lunch, 2005 March 8; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - Mantel Room Dinner #10, 2005 March 8; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - US Pharmacopeia, 2005 March 9; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - Biennial, 2005 March 15; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - 1869 Bienniail Preview and Reception, 2005 March 18; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - Truland systems Corporation, 2005 March 21; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - BPW Biennial Reception and Tour, 2005 March 24; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 28)
  - Allen Campaign Reception, 2005 March 30; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 29)
  - Southern Graphics, 2005 March 31; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 30)
  - Siegel/Baron Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2005 April 2; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 31)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 2005 April 11; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 32)
  - 1869 Cultural Cocktails, 2005 April 14; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 33)
  - Kau/Jones Wedding Ceremony and Reception, 2005 April 16; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 34)
  - Student Awards Ceremony and Reception, 2005 April 19; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 35)
  - Otto Ruesch Tribute, 2005 April 25; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 36)
  - UDC Foundation Gala, 2005 April 27; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 37)
  - Royal Netherlands Embassy, 2005 April 29; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 38)
  - Sarnoff Found for Cardiovascular Science, 2005 April 30; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 39)
  - Embraer, 2005 May 3; Series 13 (Box 89, Folder 40)
  - Schwebel/Garrett Wedding Reception, 2005 May 7; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Senior Toast, SIS Reception for Seniors, 2005 May 12; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Flint Hill School, 2005 May 15; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - CCAD Graduation, 2005 May 14; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Shomei Tomatsu Chairman's Guild Reception, 2005 May 17; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Congressional Arts Awards, 2005 May 21; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Membership Cocktails at DL's House, 2005 May 24; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - EuroUSA, 2005 May 25; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Art Reach Opening Reception, 2005 May 26; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - WHNPA Reception, 2005 May 26; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - FRIENDS Tomatsu Preview, 2005 June 2; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Brown Foreman, 2005 June 6; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - McKenna Long Aldridge LLP, 2005 June 11; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Docent Appreciation Lunch, 2005 June 14; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Sotheby's Lecture Reception, 2005 June 16; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Alliance for Young Artists and Writers, 2005 June 17; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - O'Melveny Myers LLP, 2005 June 18; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - National Foundation for Advancement in the Arts, 2005 June 26; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Schwab Advisory Network, 2005 June 27; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - FRIENDS Art Acquisition Evening, 2005 June 30; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Abramson/Maas Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2005 June 16; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Kopac-Cho wedding Ceremony Reception, 2005 July 23; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Jackie Serwer Event, 2005 July 24; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 23)
  - Department of Energy, 2005 July 26; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 24)
  - Pre-ArtCentric Kick-off Party, 2005 August 18; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 25)
  - 1869 Cultural Cocktails, 2005 September 8; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 26)
  - Mike Harreld Reception, 2005 September 8; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 27)
  - PNC/Warhol Event, 2005 September 20; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 28)
  - BPW Preview Reception, 2005 September 22; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 29)
  - Crohn's Colitis Foundation, 2005 September 24; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 30)
  - Citigroup Conference Event Planning, 2005 September 23; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 31)
  - Chariman's Guild Location, 2005 September 26; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 32)
  - Washington Center for Internships, 2005 September 27; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 33)
  - FRIENDS "ArtCentric 05" Fall Fundraiser, 2005 October 1; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 34)
  - 1869 Fall Fundraiser, 2005 October 7; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 35)
  - Gilliam Director's Circle Reception, 2005 October 10; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 36)
  - Gilliam Upper Level Opening, 2005 October 11; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 37)
  - FRIENDS Members Preview, 2005 October 14; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 38)
  - Glass/Sheffler Wedding Reception, 2005 October 15; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 39)
  - Nixon Peabody LLP, 2005 October 18; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 40)
  - Georgetown University Law Center Reunion, 2005 October 22; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 41)
  - Chevy Chase Bank, 2005 October 19; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 42)
  - EWOENAM, 2005 October 25; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 43)
  - CGA/Wachovia Congressial Reception, 2005 October 26; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 44)
  - Malcolm Pirnie, Inc., 2005 October 31; Series 13 (Box 90, Folder 45)
  - Wachovia Client Reception #1, 2005 November 2; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Steptoe Johnson LLP, 2005 November 4; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - EAG/Wachovia Family Day, 2005 November 5; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Mack/Treger Wedding Ceremony and Reception, 2005 November 5; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Warhol Art Forum, 2005 November 7; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - NIH, 2005 November 9; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - The Enterprise Social Envestment Corp., 2005 November 8; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Smithsonian Recruitment Event, 2005 November 10; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Chairman's Reception, 2005 November 10; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Lane/Buck Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2005 November 12; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - BPW Luncheon, 2005 November 15; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - Blue Pixel Seminar, 2005 November 20; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - Cisco Systems, 2005 November 16; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - EAG Education Symposium, 2005 November 17-18; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - Hyatt Hotels Resorts, 2005 November 29; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - KK Prospect Luncheon, 2005 November 22; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - Cellar Door Concert, 2005 November 30; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - New Directors Reception, 2005 December 5; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - The AES Corporation, 2005 December 2; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 19)
  - Holiday Card, 2005 December; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 20)
  - Portfolio Day, 2005 December 3; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - AFCEA-Washington Chapter, 2005 Decmeber 7; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 22)
  - Ascention Health, 2005 December 5; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 23)
  - Chairman's Guild Holiday Party, 2005 December 8; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 24)
  - Promontory Financial Group, 2005 December 9; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 25)
  - Off The Wall Art Sale, 2005 December 8-11; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 26)
  - OPM (Office of Personnel Management), 2005 December 13; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 27)
  - Dewey Ballantine LLP, 2005 December 6; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 28)
  - Wachovia Client Reception #2, 2005 December 14; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 29)
  - 1869 Member Preview "Banjo", 2005 December 15; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 30)
  - Docent Holiday Party, 2005 December 15; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 31)
  - GE Commercial Finance, 2005 December 16; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 32)
  - Blackboard, 2005 December 17; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 33)
  - Operational Technology Services, 2005 December 18; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 34)
  - Staff Holiday Party, 2005 December 19; Series 13 (Box 91, Folder 35)
  - The Advisory Board Company, 2006 January 13; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Scitor, 2006 Janaury 14; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - BPW Luncheon, 2006 January 24; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Greenhalgh Chairman's Guild Reception, 2006 January 24; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Greenhalgh BOT Dinner, 2006 January 30; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Financial Services Roundtable, 2006 January 31; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Choice Hotels, Inc., 2006 February 1; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - WPA\C Auction Opening, 2006 February 2; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - PNC Bank/BOT, 2006 February 8; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Visiting Artist Reception, 2006 February 9; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - WPA\C Gala, 2006 February 11; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - CTIA Wireless Association, 2006 February 12; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Lockheed Martin, 2006 February 21; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Oh/Brands Wedding Reception, 2006 February 25; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Bechtle Director's Circle Opening, 2006 February 28; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Robert Bechtle: A Retrospective Upper Level Opening, 2006 March 1; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - FRIENDS Bechtle Preview Reception, 2006 March 2; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - National Association of Counties, 2006 March 5; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Abramson Memorial Foundation, 2006 March 8; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Smithsonian Symposium, 2006 March 11; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Chim Opening, 2006 March 16; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Farewell Reception, 2006 March 16; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Kelly/Waylon Wedding, 2006 March 18; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - BPW Reception [Cancelled], 2006 March 16; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Bechtle Art Forum, 2006 March 21; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Leukemia Lymphoma Society, 2006 March 27; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - 1869 Chim Member Preview, 2006 March 23; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 27)
  - Smithsonian Recruitment Event, 2006 March 30; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 28)
  - QinetiQ, Inc., 2006 April 4; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 29)
  - 1869 Cultural Cocktails, 2006 April 6; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 30)
  - GW/IEEE, 2006 April 7; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 31)
  - Visiting Artist Reception, 2006 April 13; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 32)
  - CCAD Annual student Awards Cer Rec, 2006 April 18; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 33)
  - McSherry/Bildner Wedding Reception, 2006 April 22; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 34)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 2006 April 25; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 35)
  - Capitol Services Inc. (CSI), 2006 February 24; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 36)
  - PricewaterhouseCoopers, 2006 April 26; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 37)
  - KPMG, 2006 April 28; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 38)
  - Senior Opening Reception, 2006 May 4; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 39)
  - American Institute of Architects (AIA)-Aud., 2006 May 4; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 40)
  - B'nai B'rith International, 2006 May 10; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 41)
  - Senior Toast/SIS Reception for Seniors, 2006 May 11; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 42)
  - Young Presidents' Organization, 2006 May 12; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 43)
  - Butera Wedding Reception, 2006 May 13; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 44)
  - CCAD Graduation, 2006 May 13; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 45)
  - Alfred A. Knopf, 2006 May 19; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 46)
  - BOT Dinner, 2006 May 22; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 47)
  - Genworth, 2006 May 23; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 48)
  - Colby Sawyer College, 2006 May 24; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 49)
  - Botannical Treasures of Lewis Clark Reception, 2006 May 25; Series 13 (Box 96, Folder 50)
  - Allard/Goldfarb Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2006 May 28; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Escala Group/Greg Manning Aucttions, 2006 May 30; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Director's Conversion Cocktails, 2006 May 31; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - ArtReach Reception, 2006 June 1; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Director's Conversion Cocktails, 2006 June 1; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Sidley Austin, LLP, 2006 June 2; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - 1869 Spring Black Tie, 2006 June 3; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Northrop Grumman, 2006 June 7; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Friends Art Acquisition, 2006 June 8; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Docent Luncheon, 2006 June 13; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Federal Communications Bar Association, 2006 June 14; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Nordstrom Fashion Show Reception, 2006 June 20; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - O'Melveny Myers LLP, 2006 June 24; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - NFAA, 2006 June 25; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Scholastics, 2006 June 30; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Director's Cocktails, 2006; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Blanken/Gallow Ceremony Reception, 2006 July 1; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - International Corporate Governance Network, 2006 July 5; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Cleary Gottlieb Steen Hamilton, 2006 July 7; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Sutherland Asbill Brennan, 2006 July 8; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 20)
  - Weingarten Reception Dinner, 2006 July 12; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 21)
  - William Christenberry Endowment Dinner, 2006 July 14; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 22)
  - Delgado/Riecken Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2006 July 15; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 23)
  - White House News Photographers Association (WHNPA), 2006 July 20; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 24)
  - Baxt/Clemmons Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2006 August 6; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 25)
  - NETSAP, 2006 July 22; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 26)
  - MA Student Reception, Breakfast/Lunch, 2006 August 24; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 27)
  - Georgetown University Law Center Reunion, 2006 October 21; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 28)
  - Creative Coalition, 2006 September 6; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 29)
  - 1869 Cultural Cocktails, 2006 September 7; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 30)
  - Sutherland Asbill Brennan LLP, 2006 September 9; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 31)
  - AIPAC, 2006 September 12; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 32)
  - WPA/C Artist Evening, 2006 September 14; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 33)
  - Faculty/Staff Appreciation Luau, 2006 September 14; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 34)
  - Crohn's Colitis Foundation of America, 2006 September 16; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 35)
  - Bosch/Brassil Ceremony Reception, 2006 September 23; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 36)
  - Director's Luncheon, 2006 June 26; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 37)
  - Davis/Ford Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2006 September 30; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 38)
  - Board of Trustees/Ted Turner Dinner, 2006 October 11; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 39)
  - Committee of 200, 2006 October 13; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 40)
  - Vitol S.A. Inc., 2006 October 16; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 41)
  - Robert Mangold Friends/Upper Reception, 2006 October 19; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 42)
  - Faculty Exhibition Part I, 2006 October 19; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 43)
  - GWU Law School, 2006 October 21; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 44)
  - BOT Drop-Off Lunch, 2006 October 23; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 45)
  - Embassy of Romania, 2006 October 24; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 46)
  - Global Insight, 2006 October 25; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 47)
  - Brafman/Kittner Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2006 October 28; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 48)
  - The World Bank, 2006 October 30; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 49)
  - Parents Weekend Brunch, 2006 November 3; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 50)
  - Friedson/Swiller Wedding Ceremony Reception, 2006 November 4; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 51)
  - Juried Undergrad Exhibition, 2006 November 9; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 52)
  - American College of Rheumatology, 2006 November 12; Series 13 (Box 97, Folder 53)
  - Chandra Wedding Reception, 2007 September 2; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - College Faculty/Staff Appreciation Reception, 2007 September 4; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Book Signing for Mark Penn, 2007 September 5; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Alumni Jury Show, 2007 Spetember 6; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Ansel Adams Director's Circle Opening, 2007 September 11; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Ansel Adams Press Preview, 2007 September 12; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Ansel Adams New?Upper Level Opening, 2007 September 12; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - CAGW National Arts Marketing Project, 2007 September 14; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Rodger/Fletcher Wedding, 2007 September 15; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - ADH Events for Assurant Solutions, 2007 September 16; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Milton Esteron-PP Chairman's Guild, 2007 September 17; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - American Association of Advertising Agencies, 2007 September 17; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Janet Solinger's Celebration, 2007 September 18; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Shaw Contract Group, 2007 September 19; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - BPW/Ric Burns Reception, 2007 September 20; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Ogilvy Goverment Relations for AIG Investment, 2007 September 26; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Alper 80th Birthday Party, 2007 September 30; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - National Foreign Trade Council, 2007 October 2; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Papermakers Reception-College, 2007 October 4; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Booz Allen Hamilton, 2007 October 6; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Annie Leibovitz Opening, 2007 October 9; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Annie Leibovitz Press Preview, 2007 October 9; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - Levada/Kurz Ceremony Reception (Cancelled), 2007 October 13; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Swiss Re, 2007 October 14; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - Sally Martin Reception/PP [Press Preview], 2007 September 25; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - WCTC September Meeting, 2007 September 26; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - World Wildlife Fund, 2007 October 16; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - Experient Inc. for AT, 2007 October 17; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - 1869 Cultural Cocktails, 2007 October 18; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - GEP Washington for Merill Lynch, 2007 October 19; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - Georgetown University Law Center, 2007 October 20; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - Smithsonian Women's Committee, 2007 October 24; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - Venable LLP Partners' Event, 2007 October 24; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - Jeremy Blake Memorial Service, 2007 October 26; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - Jeremy Blake Memorial, 2007 October 26; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - Lim/Sheren Wedding Reception, 2007 October 27; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 36)
  - WPA Annual Meeting, 2007 October 29; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 37)
  - Silgan Containers, 2007 October 30; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 38)
  - Foundation for the NIH, 2007 October 31; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 39)
  - Torkwase Dyson Reception, 2007 November 1; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 40)
  - BAE Systems Inc., 2007 November 3; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 41)
  - National Air and Transportaion Association, 2007 November 5; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 42)
  - Sidley Austin LLP, 2007 November 6; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 43)
  - Exxon Mobile, 2007 November 7; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 44)
  - Chrysler Musuem Lunch, 2007 November 9; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 45)
  - GEP for American Nuclear Society, 2007 November 12; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 46)
  - Art Forum Luncheon, 2007 November 13; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 47)
  - Master's Programs Open House, 2007 November 15; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 48)
  - Vanity Fair for Charles Schwab, 2007 November 15; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 49)
  - Arnold and Porter, 2007 November 16; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 50)
  - BPW Luncheon, 2007 November 27; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 51)
  - Interface Flor, 2007 November 28; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 52)
  - The Plasencia Group, Inc., 2007 November 29; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 53)
  - New Members Orientation, 2007 November 29; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 54)
  - Press Previews, 2007 November; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 55)
  - Watson Wyatt Company Holiday Event, 2007 December 1; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 56)
  - National Portfolio Day, 2007 December 1; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 57)
  - Pricewaterhouse Coopers, 2007 December 3; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 58)
  - The Freedom Project (Friends of John Boehner), 2007 December 5; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 59)
  - Off the Walls Art Sale, 2007 December 6-8; Series 13 (Box 98, Folder 60)